<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ Bear Blog</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ Bear Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:39:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hibernating to an Encrypted Swapfile on BTRFS with NixOS</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/hibernating-to-an-encrypted-swapfile-on-btrfs-with-nixos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:39:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/hibernating-to-an-encrypted-swapfile-on-btrfs-with-nixos/</guid>
      <description>Hibernating to an Encrypted Swapfile on BTRFS with NixOS Note that BTRFS swapfiles across multiple devices (pools, RAIDs) are not supported.
BTRFS on Linux kernels before version 5.0 can result in FS corruption. From the Arch Wiki:
Btrfs on Linux kernel before version 5.0 does not support swap files. Failure to heed this warning may result in file system corruption. While a swap file may be used on Btrfs when mounted through a loop device, this will result in severely degraded swap performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 13:32:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/test-post/</guid>
      <description>hello!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Newcomer&#39;s Commentary on 3D Printing</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/a-newcomers-commentary-on-3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/a-newcomers-commentary-on-3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>After recently purchasing my first 3D printer, I have developed some thoughts on the technology in general.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had friends in the 3D printing scene preach the virtues of the technology for years now. Still, I was unconvinced. It seemed like quite an expensive investment for the infrequent payoff of being able to print something useful. After all, I could always fall back on my friends who did own 3D printers if I needed something printed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soldering Tips From Experience</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/soldering-tips-from-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/soldering-tips-from-experience/</guid>
      <description>Soldering is an indispensable skill for countless fields of interest, from electric luthierie to car repair. While I am not a master at soldering, I hope by sharing what I have learned I may help beginners struggling to solder clean joints.
Safety Soldering can be a dangerous activity. There are high temperatures and toxic fumes involved, but with proper precautions, most health risks can be minimized.
As a disclaimer, I am not a medical expert and take no liability for any injuries you may sustain from following (or not following) these safety tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: A Sand County Almanac</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/book-review-a-sand-county-almanac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/book-review-a-sand-county-almanac/</guid>
      <description>Written by environmentalist Aldo Leopold, A Sand County Almanac is one of the most elegant pieces of nature writing I have ever read. While only formally educated in forestry, Leopold displays a mastery of language in his stunning descriptions of outwardly simple experiences.
The novel is well-known in conservation circles for pioneering the idea of land ethic&amp;mdash;the concept that the natural world can only be protected by instilling respect and a sense of responsibility for the land we live on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Version 0.1.0</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/can-version-0-1-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/can-version-0-1-0/</guid>
      <description>I have released my program Can on RubyGems and the Arch User Repository.
Introduction I have a feeling this post is going to get hairy with a program name like Can!
Can is an idea for a program I&amp;rsquo;ve had for a very long time. As the FreeDesktop.org trash specification says, &amp;ldquo;An ability to recover accidentally deleted files has become the de facto standard for today&amp;rsquo;s desktop user experience.&amp;rdquo; But what about a user&amp;rsquo;s command-line experience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Response to Log4shell</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/my-response-to-log4shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/my-response-to-log4shell/</guid>
      <description>I have remodeled my entire server stack to better defend against critical vulnerabilities.
I know this blogpost is long overdue, with the waves Log4Shell sent through the security world having mostly passed, but I promise my action was timely!
Background Previously, my server ran Debian 11 (Bullseye) with a custom sandboxing SystemD configuration for every service I ran (read more about my old setup here). This approach offered performance benefits at the extreme cost of my time&amp;mdash;it takes ages to work out all the kinks in a custom configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2021 KSU HS CTF Writeup</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/fall-2021-ksu-hs-ctf-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/fall-2021-ksu-hs-ctf-writeup/</guid>
      <description>I placed third at the end of the challenge, winning myself $50. This is how I solved the hardest and least-solved questions of each category.
Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to work on my resume recently, and what better way to do it than with a fun CTF organized by a local college? The competition ran from 10 A.M. to 3:30 P.M. on Sunday, November 13th. There were 33 applicants (including myself), 26 of which competed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Started My Server</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/how-i-started-my-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/how-i-started-my-server/</guid>
      <description>My server used to be an old gaming desktop, now running Debian 11. I publish my blog with a custom static site generator written in Ruby.
Hardware This website is running off an old midrange gaming computer, from circa 12 years ago. I received it for free from a friend, who himself also got it for free from an elderly neighbor.
The specs are as follows:
MSI K9N6PGM2-V2 Motherboard AMD Athalon II X2 250 NVIDIA GeForce 8600 GT 2x2GB 400MHz DDR2 Memory The computer had no drive, so I bought a 256GB SATA SSD and slapped it in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sawyer I&amp;rsquo;m a college student currently studying for an associate degree in cybersecurity, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to get some certs as well. I love playing and listening to music&amp;mdash;I play all sorts of instruments, including guitar, banjo, cajon, keyboard, and bass guitar. Alternative rock and grunge are my favorite genres. I&amp;rsquo;ve also recently become interested in backpacking.
A few of my friends have cool blogs you should check out as well:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
